smartlook.com 2019-06-23

# Privacy statement - Smartlook

Smartlook is developed and operated by Smartsupp.com, s.r.o., VAT ID : CZ03668681.

Started in 2016, [Smartlook provides qualitative website](https://www.smartlook.com/) and [mobile app analytics](https://www.smartlook.com/features/mobile) with [always-on visitor recordings](https://www.smartlook.com/features/recordings), [automatic event tracking](https://www.smartlook.com/features/events), [conversion funnels](https://www.smartlook.com/features/funnels), and [heatmaps for websites](https://www.smartlook.com/features/heatmaps). Not just numbers and graphs, Smartlook helps websites & apps owners to truly understand their users’ actions.

With Smartlook all user personal information is considered private. Smartlook does not share any personal information of its users with 3rd parties.

## Where is personal information stored?

Smartlook runs on Amazon AWS cloud infrastructure. We use Amazon AWS data center in Frankfurt, Germany, where data and personal information is processed and stored. Data is not stored or being sent outside of European Union in any way. You can read more about Amazon AWS data privacy [here](https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-privacy-faq/).

Smartlook takes data security very seriously. We handle data and personal information according to EU laws and regulations, which are one of the strictest in the world. Smartlook will be compliant with the new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) when it comes into effect on 25th May 2018. Amazon AWS, where Smartlook server infrastructure is running, provides extensive details on [its EU Data Protection compliance](https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/eu-data-protection/) and also will be GDPR compliant once it comes in effect.

## How is personal information secured?

Smartlook protects personal information with use of the latest industry standards and security measures. Smartlook uses SSL/TLS encryption (secure sockets layer / transport layer security) for protection of user data and personal information.

A Smartlook user can access and update personal information after signing in to the Smartlook account located under the dashboard page. To sign in, the user is required to know his/her login credentials – email address and password. There is no way to access personal information without knowing the login credentials, therefore no unauthorized party can access it.

## What kind of personal information is being collected?

Smartlook.com might, but is not obliged to, collect following information. All personal information mentioned below is considered private and is handled according to this privacy statement.

**1\. User personal information:**  Upon account creation the user is required to fill in his email address and a password. The user can update this information after signing in to his/her account on <https://www.smartlook.com/>. Also any other personal data that visitors enters on Smartlook website or inside the application might be collected by Smartlook.

**2\. Visitor personal information:**  Each Smartlook user has an option to disable recording of form inputs on his website inside Smartlook application. If the user chooses to record form inputs, any personal data his/her visitors might fill in those form inputs is collected by Smartlook. User might be legally required to inform visitors that their personal data are being collected by Smartlook as a 3rd party.

Every Smartlook user has access to personal information of visitors on their website where Smartlook code is used. Because a visitor may provide personal information on a Smartlook users website, this creates a legal relation between the Smartlook user and the visitor. Smartlook users can access and handle the personal information of their visitors collected by Smartlook. Each Smartlook user handles the personal information of his/her visitors according to his/her own privacy statement and/or terms & conditions.

**3\. Technical information:**  while using Smartlook, certain data about visitors might be collected to improve the Smarlook product, e.g. IP address, type and version of browser, type and version of operating system, approximate location, etc.

## How do we use Cookie files?

While using Smartlook, temporary files, known as Cookie files, can be stored and processed. By processing cookie files personal information might be collected and linked with the visitor. This personal information is used solely to improve the Smartlook services. Smartlook respects privacy of its users and visitors and while processing Cookie files we follow the privacy rules of the European Union.

A visitor can prevent collection and storing of Cookie files by turning off Cookies, or browsing the web in Incognito (private) mode, where he/she remains anonymous. This mode is supported in all modern browsers. By doing so, the user acknowledges that Smartlook services might not work properly and that use of Smartlook services can exhibit unexpected behavior.

## Changes of this privacy statement

Smartlook reserves the right to change or update this privacy statement without further notice. It is recommended that users check this privacy statement regularly to have the latest information about Smartlook.com privacy policy. An up-to-date version of this privacy statement can always be found on our website <https://www.smartlook.com/>
